http://www.jandenul.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Jan De Nul understands that privacy is very important to you and we do our best to respect it.
The sections below detail how Jan De Nul handles your personal data when you use our services, when you visit our websites or when you otherwise deal with a Jan De Nul affiliate. By using any of our services including our website or otherwise dealing with us and by providing us with any personal information, you are consenting to the use of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy.
Please do not send us any personal information if you do not want your personal information to be used in the way described herein.
This Privacy Policy applies to all processing activities by the Jan De Nul group of companies, whether acting as data controller or as data processor.
Collection and Use of Personal Data
If you want to use our services or when you otherwise deal with an entity of the Jan De Nul group of companies, you may be asked for some personal data, such as your first and last name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, mobile number, date of birth, language and other personal data which we deem necessary or useful.
Personal data can be collected through various channels: e.g. orally, by telephone, in writing or through electronic forms on our websites (for example, the vacancy application facility in the "Jobs" section of our website).
When collecting personal data the purpose of collecting is apparent at the point that you provide your personal information and we only use your information for those purposes. If Jan De Nul would want to process your personal data for a purpose other than that for which it was collected, we will contact you beforehand with information on that purpose and with any other relevant information.
The personal data you provide us through different channels is stored in files held by Jan De Nul NV (Tragel 60, 9308 Hofstade (Belgium)). The personal data is used for:
To provide and improve our websites.
To provide and improve our services to you.
To compile anonymous statistics, for example, website usage statistics.
To market our services.
To manage our relationship with you.
To fulfil our legal or contractual obligations.
For the purposes of recruitment.
For other legitimate business purposes.
The personal data is stored for up to 5 years after a person has ceased its dealings with Jan De Nul unless otherwise indicated at the time of collecting your personal data.
Lawfulness of Processing Personal Data
Jan De Nul is committed only to process personal data of a data subject if at least one of the following applie
the data subject has given consent to the processing of his or her personal data for one or more specific purposes;
processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract;
processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the controller is subject;
processing is necessary in order to protect the vital interests of the data subject or of another natural person;
processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the controller or by a third party, except where such interests are overridden by the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject which require protection of personal data.
Processing of special categories of personal data (if any) and processing of personal data not received from the data subject will be executed in compliance with The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679).
Protection of Personal Data
We apply the highest standard of security when it comes to safeguarding and protecting personal data. We have taken technical and organizational measures to protect the databases in which your personal data is kept against unauthorized access, unauthorized use, theft or loss. Our security measures are regularly evaluated and adapted so that we can continue to provide a high level of protection.
Jan De Nul shall report any serious security breach to the authorities and/or the data subject and/or the data controller as per applicable law or contractual provisions if it becomes aware that the security, confidentiality or integrity of personal data has been compromised.
Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties
We do not make personal information available to any third party, except with your prior permission or when such disclosure is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are party or when Jan De Nul is obliged to do so in accordance with applicable law and regulations.
Any information that you provide to us may be shared with and processed by any entity in the worldwide network of Jan De Nul group of companies. This may entail a transfer of your information from a location within the European Economic Area (the "EEA") to outside the EEA, or from outside the EEA to a location within the EEA. The level of information protection in countries outside the EEA may be less than that offered within the EEA, however we have procedures in place to ensure the protection of your information up to the level required within the EEA.
While it is unlikely, we may be required to disclose your information to comply with legal or regulatory requirements. We will use reasonable endeavours to notify you before we do this, unless we are legally restricted from doing so.
Privacy Policy in relation to our Websites
Connection Data
We register a limited set of information about connections that are made to our websites and the software and devices that are used to accomplish this. This data is used to create statistics and improve the quality of our websites and services through analyses of your surfing behavior on our websites. No personal data in relation to connection data are collected or processed by Jan De Nul.
Cookie Policy
A cookie is a text file that is installed in the browser of your computer or mobile device by a website's server when you consult a website. The cookie contains a unique code which makes it possible for your browser to be recognized when you visit the website ("session" cookies) or during subsequent, repeated visits ("permanent" cookies). Cookies can be installed by the server of the website you visit or by partners of that website. A website's server can only read the cookies it has installed itself, and has no access to other information found in your computer or mobile device. Cookies are stored in the folder of your browser on your computer or mobile device. A cookie usually consists of the name of the server that placed the cookie, an expiry date, and a unique number code.
Cookies generally make the interaction between the visitor and the website faster and easier, and help the visitor navigate between the different parts of a website. Cookies can also be used to make the content or advertisement on a website more relevant for the visitor, and can be adapted to his personal taste and needs.
Jan De Nul websites make use of such cookies.
Hyperlinks
Our websites may contain hyperlinks to websites that are not managed by Jan De Nul. Such hyperlinks are provided purely for information purposes. When consulting such websites, we recommend that you carefully read their privacy policy.
Your Rights
Under applicable data protection legislation we will use reasonable endeavours to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. Therefore, please advise us of any changes to your information.
You are entitled to request details of the information we hold about you and to have it rectified or erased as allowed by applicable data protection legislation. You may object to or restrict the processing of your personal data in accordance with the applicable data protection legislation. If the processing of personal data is based on your explicit consent you may withdraw your consent at any time without affecting the lawfulness of processing such data prior to such withdrawal.
You have the right to receive the personal data you have provided us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and you have the right to transmit this data to another controller without hindrance from us where (i) the processing is based on your explicit consent or on a contract with yourself; and (ii) the processing is carried out by automated means.
If you receive marketing materials from us, you may withdraw your consent for us to send these to you at any time and free of charge by sending an e-mail to Jan De Nul.
Changes in our Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy may be extended or adapted in the future (for example, to accommodate new developments). For this reason, we recommend that you consult this privacy policy regularly.
We further reserve all rights to make ad hoc changes to this Privacy Policy on a case by case basis to suit a specific personal data collection process. In such case, deviations from this Privacy Policy will be made apparent at the moment you provide your personal information.
Contact Details
Sofidra S.A with registered office in 34-36, Parc d’Activités Capellen, L-8308 Capellen, Grand Duchy of Luxemburg, registered under number B 73.723, is the party responsible for processing your personal data.
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact the controller  or  the data protection offer through privacy@jandenul.com
Complaints
Any complaint against Jan De Nul in relation to the processing of your personal data can be lodged with any competent supervisory authority.
Jan De Nul Group shapes water and land. Through a creative and innovative approach, we achieve sustainable and successful results. With us, the client can rest assured. Today, but also tomorrow.
https://www.facebook.com/jandenulgroup
https://twitter.com/jandenulgroup
https://www.instagram.com/jandenulgroup
https://www.linkedin.com/company/jan-de-nul/
https://www.youtube.com/user/JDNGroupOfficial
About us
Vision, Mission, Values
History
